Guide to the Nicholas School of the Environment's Senior Professional Program Records, 1977-1997
Duke University. University Archives
Nicholas School of the Environment's Senior Professional Program records 1977-1997
Duke University. University Archives
Nicholas School of the Environment (Duke University). Senior Professional Program.
10.5 linear feet Extent: 7000 Items
The Nicholas School of the Environment's Senior Professional Program traces its beginnings to 1979, when the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies first offered a program of short intensive courses. These courses have been offered since then as part of various named programs and centers, including the Intensive Course Program, the Continuing Education Program, and the Center for Environmental Education. As of 2013, the Senior Professional Program is the only one of these terms that remains in use as a formally named entity in the Nicholas School. The Nicholas School of the Environment's Senior Professional Program Records span the years 1977-1997 and contain correspondence with faculty, syllabi, notebooks, schedules, and other materials from intensive courses, workshops, and conferences offered as part of the Intensive Course Program, the Center for Continuing Education, the Center for Environmental Education, and the Senior Professional Program. Materials document research and teaching interests of several Nicholas School faculty, and topics covered in the courses include ecological risk assessment, environmental sciences, water supply, water resources development, forest management, and the National Environmental Policy Act. Arranged in order by accession number.
UA.18.04.0001
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Nicholas School of the Environment, Senior Professional Program Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer, 1993-1999.
Historical Note
The Nicholas School of the Environment's Senior Professional Program traces its beginnings to 1979, when the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies first began offering a program of short intensive courses to professionals in the fields of forestry and environmental studies. Over the years since then, the original curriculum has expanded steadily and the courses have been offered under the auspices of a variety of named programs and centers from the 1980s through the early 2000s, including the Intensive Course Program, the Continuing Education Program, the Center for Environmental Education, and the Senior Professional Program. The Nicholas School continues to offer a variety of intensive and continuing education courses, but as of 2013 the Senior Professional Program is the only one of these terms in use as a formally named entity.
Collection Overview
The Nicholas School of the Environment, Senior Professional Program Records contain correspondence with faculty, syllabi, notebooks, schedules, and other materials from courses, workshops, and conferences presented under the auspices of several Nicholas School programs and centers from 1977-1997, including the Intensive Course Program, the Center for Continuing Education, the Center for Environmental Education, and the Senior Professional Program. These materials document the research and teaching interests of several Nicholas School faculty during this period; topics covered in the courses include ecological risk assessment, environmental sciences, water supply, water resources development, forest management, and the National Environmental Policy Act. Some materials have been transferred to this collection from the Nicholas School of the Environment Records, 1916-2010. The collection is arranged in order by accession number.
Subject Headings
Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University. Nicholas School of the Environment. Center for Continuing Education; Duke University. Nicholas School of the Environment. Senior Professional Program; Nicholas School of the Environment and Earth Sciences (Duke University) -- History; Continuing education -- North Carolina -- Durham; Ecological risk assessment -- North Carolina; Environmental impact analysis -- North Carolina; Environmental management -- North Carolina; Environmental sciences -- North Carolina; Environmental sciences -- Study and teaching; Forest management -- North Carolina; United States. National Environmental Policy Act of 1969; Water-supply -- North Carolina; Water resources development -- Environmental aspects -- North Carolina
Related Material
Nicholas School of the Environment Records, 1916-2010.
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Accession UA 1993-0106, 1977-1989, (2 boxes)
  Syllabi, correspondence with instructors and participants, printed matter, and other materials offered in intensive courses from 1977-1989, most often as part of the Intensive Course Program or the Senior Professional Program. Arranged as received; all folders are syllabi unless otherwise described.
  [Restricted until 2014.]
  - Forest Management--Sizemore, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Gelbert, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Regional Resource Planning--Hart, 1978 Nov. 6-17 (Box 1)
  - Analyzing Forest Resources for Industry--Guttenberg, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Legal Aspects of Land Use--Cummings, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Economics of Fire Management--Vasievich, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Forest Policy--Clawson, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Peat for Energy--McMullen/Harwood, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Economics for Public Land Managers and Planners--Convery, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Biology of Urban Trees--Perry, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Water Resource Management Policy--Stickley, undated (Box 1)
  - Management Decisions in Forestry--White, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Forest Policy--Clawson, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Forest Economics--Clawson, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Interpretation of Aerial Photos/Remote Sensing--Baker, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Environmental Law--Thomas, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Property Law and Land Use Planning--Thomas, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Natural Resource Law--Thomas, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Suffolk County, Long Island: A Case Study of Significant Environmental Problems--Cummings, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal--Sizemore, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Economics in Forest Planning and Program Implementation--Row, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Management of Southern Hardwood Forests--McKnight, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Natural Resource Conflict Management--Busterud, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Economics of Intensive Forestry--Dutrow, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Management of Forestry Research--Bentley, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Special Tax Problems of Industrial Timberland Owners--Condrell, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Legislation Regulations of Private Forest Practices in the United States--Siegel, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Constraints to the Effectiveness of Urban Forestry Management--Perry, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Forest Policy--Clawson, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Peat for Energy--McMullan, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Management of Southern Hardwood Forests--McKnight, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Duke Timber Valuation Seminar--Condrell, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Computer Applications for Forest Managers--Vasievich, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Water Resource Management Policy--Stickley, 1982 (Box 1)
  - "Natural Resource, People and Management"--Bentley, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Special Tax Problems of Industrial Timberland Owners--Condrell, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Urban Forest Management--Perry, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Writing for Result in Forest and Environmental Industries--House, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Special Tax Problems of Industrial Timberland Owners--Condrell, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Natural Resource Conflict Management--Busterud, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Choices in Silviculture--Boyce, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Water Resource Management--Stickley, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell, 1983 Nov. 14-18 (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; syllabus, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, 1984 Fall (Box 1)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell, 1984 Fall (Box 1)
  - Special Tax Problems of Industrial Timberland Owners--Condrell, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Economics of Intensive Forestry--Dutrow, 1985 Spring (Box 1)
  - Choices in Silviculture--Boyce, 1985 Fall (Box 1)
  - Mathematical Modeling of Lake and Reservoir Water Quality--Reckhow, 1985 Mar. (Box 1)
  - Economics of Intensive Forestry--Vasievich, 1986 Spring (Box 1)
  - Business Aspects of Natural Resource Management--MacKinnon, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Mathematical Modeling of Lake and Reservoir Water Quality--Reckhow, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Elements of Forestry--MacKinnon, 1987 Spring (Box 1)
  - Dynamic Modeling--Boyce, 1987 Fall (Box 1)
  - Hazardous Waste Management--Davidson, 1987 Spring (Box 1)
  - Environmental Conflict Management--Busterud, 1987 Spring (Box 1)
  - Environmental Law--Heath, 1987 Spring (Box 1)
  - Forest Nutrition Management--Binkley/Allen, 1987 Spring (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore, 1987 Fall (Box 1)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore, 1987 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - USDA Forest Service--Boyce; correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Mathematical Modeling--Reckhow, 1987 Fall (Box 1)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; correspondence with instructor, 1988 Spring (Box 1)
  - Environmental Law--Heath; syllabus, correspondence with instructor and participants, 1988 Spring, (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Timberland Investments--Howard/Mason; correspondence with instructor, 1988 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell; correspondence with instructor, 1988 Spring (Box 2)
  - Hazard Waste Management:The RCRA Program--Davidson; correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Modeling of Forestry--Boyce; correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Special Tax Problems of Industrial Timberland Owners--Condrell; correspondence with instructor and participants, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, 1988 Fall (Box 2)
  - Introduction to Geographic Information Systems (GIS)--Berry; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Mathematical Modeling of Lake and Reservoir Water Quality--Chapra/Reckhow; correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Resource Management Decisions I--MacKinnon; correspondence with instructor, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Law--Heath; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Forest Taxation--Condrell; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hazardous Waste Management: The Superfund Program--Davidson; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Negotiating and Resolving Environmental and Public Policy Disputes--Bingham/Orenstein; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Implementation of the National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA) on Federal Lands and Facilities--Clark; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Timberland Investments--Howard/Mason; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
- Accession UA 1994-0102, 1989-1992, (1 box)
  Syllabi, correspondence with instructors and participants, printed matter, and other materials offered in intensive courses from 1989-1992 as part of the Senior Professional Program. Arranged as received; all folders are syllabi unless otherwise described.
  [Restricted until 2017.]
  - Financial Management: The Key to Sound Resource Management--MacKinnon; syllabus, correspondence with instructor and with participants, 1989 June, (3 folders) (Box 2)
    [Restricted until 2015.]
  - Dynamic Modeling of Forestry--Boyce/Easterling; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hazardous Waste Management: The RCRA Program--Davidson; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Financial Management--MacKinnon; syllabus, correspondence with instructor and with participants, 1989 Oct., (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - NEPA--Clark; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Environmental Toxicology and Risk Assessment--Reckhow/Di Giulio; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Introduction to GIS--Berry; correspondence with instructor, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, 1990 Spring (Box 2)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; correspondence with instructor, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Financial Management--MacKinnon; syllabus, correspondence with instructor and with participants, 1990 Feb., (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Mathematical Modeling--Chapra/Reckhow; correspondence with instructor, 1990 Feb. (Box 2)
  - Elements of Forestry--MacKinnon; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Mar., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hazardous Waste Management: The Superfund Program--Davidson; correspondence with instructor, 1990 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Environmental Law--Heath; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Apr., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Financial Management--MacKinnon; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 June, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - NEPA--Clark; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1990 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Modeling of Forestry and Natural Resource Management Strategies--Boyce/Easterling; correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall (Box 2)
  - Nonpoint Pollution Control for Forestry and Agriculture--Hansard/McIntyre; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - The Safe Drinking Water Act and Amendment--Ginley/Patrizi; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hazardous Waste Management: The RCRA Program--Davidson; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1990 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Environmental Toxicology and Risk Assessment--Reckhow/Di Giulio; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Mar., (2 folders) (Box 2)
    [Restricted until 2016.]
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Mar., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hazardous Waste Management: The Superfund Program--Davidson; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Apr., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Conservation Land Acquisition--Ludington; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Sept., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); syllabus, correspondence with participants, 1991 Sept., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Army National Guard NEPA Course--Clark; correspondence with instructor, 1991 Nov. (Box 2)
  - NEPA--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - The Domestic and Global Characteristics of the Pulp and Paper Business--Slinn; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Dec., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath, 1992 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Coastal Zone Management--Brower/Owens; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Mar., (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Feb., (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Mar., (2 folders) (Box 2)
- Accession UA 1996-0080, 1991-1993, (2 boxes)
  Syllabi, correspondence with instructors and participants, printed matter, and other materials offered in intensive courses from 1991-1993 as part of the Senior Professional Program. Arranged as received; all folders are syllabi unless otherwise described.
  [Restricted until 2018.]
  - Timberland Investments--Howard/Mason; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1991 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Applied Forest Inventory--Borders/Shiver; correspondence with instructor, 1992 Fall (Box 2)
  - Conservation Land Acquisition--Ludington; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Dynamic Modeling--Boyce/Austin; syllabus, correspondence with instructor and participants, 1992 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Environmental Planning and Land Development--Kilby; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - The Monitoring of Hazardous Air Pollutants--Winberry/Crume/Lapp; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - The National Environmental Policy Act(NEPA)--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Army National Guard NEPA Course--Magness/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - The Domestic and Global Characteristics of the Forest Products Business--Slinn/Goetzl; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Applied Groundwater Flow Modeling--Eimers; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Environmental Toxicology and Risk Assessment--Di Giulio/Reckhow/Faust; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1992 Spring, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; correspondence with participants, 1992 Spring (Box 3)
  - Mathematical Modeling of Lake and Reservoir Water Quality--Chapra/Reckhow; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1992 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Air Quality Management--Vandenberg/Cote; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Coastal Zone Management--Brower/Owens, 1993 Spring (Box 3)
  - Energy: Engineering, Economic and Policy Perspectives--Hill/Gordon/Riggs/Bisesi; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Environmental Toxicology and Risk Assessment--Di Giulio/Reckhow/Faust; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Field Ornithology: Spring Bird Study on the Coast--Spitzer; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Negotiation Skills for Settling Public Disputes--Godschalk/Sachs; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - NEPA--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Army National Guard NEPA Course--Magness; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Nonpoint Source Pollution Control for Forestry and Agriculture--McIntyre; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Timberland Investments--Howard/Mason; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Watershed Management for Water Supply Protection; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Environmental Planning and Land Development--Kilby; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
- Accession UA 1997-0072, 1993-1994, (2 boxes)
  Syllabi, correspondence with instructors and participants, printed matter, and other materials offered in intensive courses from 1993-1994, most often as part of the Continuing Education Program. Arranged as received; all folders are syllabi unless otherwise described.
  [Restricted until 2019.]
  - Financial Management--MacKinnon, 1993 Spring (Box 3)
  - Reporting the Results of Forestland Appraisals--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Aug., (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Dynamic Modeling of Forestry and Natural Resource Management Strategies--Boyce/Austin, 1993 Fall (Box 3)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); financial, 1993 Fall (Box 3)
  - Conservation Land Acquisition--Ludington, 1993 Fall (Box 3)
  - Reporting the Results of Forestland Appraisals--Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - NEPA--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Army National Guard NEPA Course--Magness; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1993 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - The Domestic and Global Characteristics of the Pulp and Paper Business--Slinn; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1993 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Field Ornithology: Spring Bird Study on the Coast--Spitzer; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Preparation of Environmental Assessments and Impact Statements--Magness; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Forest Appraisal I--Sizemore; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Forest Appraisal II--Sizemore; correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring (Box 3)
  - Basic Ground-Water Hydrology--Heath; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Negotiation Skills for Settling Public Disputes--Godschalk/Sachs; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - NEPA--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Environmental Planning and Land Development--Kilby; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Spring, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - NEPA--Clark/Soloman; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Medicine for the Third World Traveler--Maeyens/Corey; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - The Domestic and Global Characteristics of the Pulp and Paper Business--Slinn; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Forest Appraisal--Musselman/Sizemore (Portland, Ore.); syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Preparing and Documenting Environmental Impact Analyses--Magness; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, instructor evaluations, 1994 Fall, (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Models for Landscape Forestry: Meeting Consumers Demands--Boyce/Austin; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Army National Guard NEPA Course--Magness; syllabus, correspondence with instructor, 1994 Fall, (2 folders) (Box 4)